<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Carrollton News RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/</link><description>
          This is the syndication feed for City of Carrollton, TX.
          Carrollton News</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:48:22 -0500</lastBuildDate><item><title>Severe Weather Cleanup Updates</title><description>July 15
6:00 p.m.
Collection crews have completed or are in progress with a first pass of 93.4 percent of streets in Carrollton, with 71,055 cubic yards of storm debris out of an estimated 100,000–150,000 cubic yards collected. Due to the progress...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4737/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:59:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4737/?date=20240715055900</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Reports Positive Mosquito Traps</title><description>Click to view PDF&amp;nbsp;
        
    









Dallas County Health and Human Services (DCHHS) has confirmed two mosquito samples testing positive for West Nile Virus (WNV) in Carrollton. The samples were collected from...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4746/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 15:58:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4746/?date=20240715035800</guid></item><item><title>NTTA Closing The Addison Tunnel Daily Through July 18</title><description>NTTA TRAFFIC ADVISORY
Various Daily Closures for NTTA Maintenance: These closures are needed for tunnel upgrades. 
July 8-11 from 9 a.m to 4 p.m. (Daily):
East- and westbound Addision Airport Toll Tunnel (AATT) will be closed to traffic daily.
July...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/3766/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:40:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/3766/?date=20240709054000</guid></item><item><title>DART to Reduce Weekend Rail Service in Dallas During Repairs</title><description>Passengers traveling in Dallas’ Central Business District via DART may experience delays over at the weekends of June 28-July 1 and July 12-15 as necessary maintenance is performed on DART Rail’s high-voltage power source — or catenary — via a...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4753/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:16:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4753/?date=20240630021600</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Marketing Services Wins Three State Awards</title><description>&amp;nbsp;
        
    

The City of Carrollton Marketing Services Department was honored to be recognized with three state marketing and communications awards, including two first-place awards,...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4751/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 08:23:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4751/?date=20240627082300</guid></item><item><title>City Council Increases Senior and Disabled Homestead Tax Exemptions</title><description>Carrollton City Council voted unanimously to approve an amendment to an ordinance increasing the senior and disabled tax exemptions from $87,000 to $97,000 at the Tuesday, June 25 meeting.
The ordinance as amended is effective immediately and applies...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4750/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:28:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4750/?date=20240626042800</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Selects New Pro Tem Positions</title><description>&amp;nbsp;
            
            
        
        
            
            &amp;nbsp;Mayor Pro Tem Richard Fleming
            
            &amp;nbsp;
            &amp;nbsp;Deputy Mayor Pro Tem Christopher Axberg...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4749/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4749/?date=20240626042400</guid></item><item><title>Volunteer for Carrollton’s CARE Team</title><description>Carrollton stands as the first city in Texas to adopt the groundbreaking 4 Minute City™ Program. This initiative aims to equip CPR-trained citizen volunteers with AEDs, thereby reducing the time required to provide lifesaving care to patients...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4659/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 08:27:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4659/?date=20240626082700</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Ranks Among the Top Safest Cities Nationwide</title><description>The City of Carrollton ranks among the top 25 safest cities nationwide on GOBankingRates’ “50 Safest and Most Affordable US Cities To Live In” report. 
According to GOBankingRates’ May review of the largest U.S. cities by population, Carrollton has...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4743/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4743/?date=20240618042400</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Seeks Citizen Input for Downtown Expansion</title><description>The City of Carrollton is expanding its Downtown Master Plan to develop the area near the Dallas Area Rapid Transit (DART) Green Line Light Rail. Don’t miss the opportunity to make a difference.
The objective of the expansion is to build on the...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4706/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 09:37:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4706/?date=20240611093700</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton to Provide Special Collection of Storm Debris</title><description>The City of Carrollton has contracted with current provider Republic Services and CrowderGulf Disaster Recovery &amp;amp; Debris Management to conduct a special collection of storm debris at residential addresses, beginning Monday, June 3....</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4741/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:30:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4741/?date=20240603013000</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton to Host Eighth Annual Paws on the Square Event</title><description>Bring the whole family, both furry and otherwise, to Historic Downtown Carrollton (1106 S. Broadway Street) on Saturday, June 8, from 9 a.m. to noon, for a tail-wagging good time at the City’s eighth annual Paws on the Square. This free,...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4713/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4713/?date=20240603010000</guid></item><item><title>Festival at the Switchyard Vendor Applications Now Open</title><description>The City of Carrollton has opened applications for craft and food vendors to participate in the 14th annual Festival at the Switchyard on Saturday, November 2 from 11 a.m. to 10 p.m. in Historic Downtown Carrollton (1106 S. Broadway Street).
The...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4729/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4729/?date=20240603124800</guid></item><item><title>Trinity River Authority Sanitary Sewer Outflow Notice Due to Heavy Rain</title><description>The Trinity River Authority has notified the City of Carrollton that its Central Regional Wastewater System treatment plant experienced a wastewater outflow in its collection system on Tuesday, May 28, that exceeded 100,000 gallons. It occurred in an...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4739/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:03:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4739/?date=20240529040300</guid></item><item><title>Take Carrollton's Parks &amp; Recreation Master Plan Survey</title><description>The City of Carrollton is updating its Parks, Recreation, and Open Space Master Plan, and is gathering input from residents on what they envision in the years ahead for their children and for themselves.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
TAKE THE SURVEY
Survey is...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4677/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:13:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4677/?date=20240528091300</guid></item><item><title>Help Turn the Page Through Carrollton Public Library's Survey</title><description>In an effort to continue providing high level services to both existing and future patrons, the Carrollton Public Library has opened a survey opportunity to the community.
The survey is anonymous and open to everyone through Monday, July 1. The...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4727/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 08:49:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4727/?date=20240528084900</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton to Hold Memorial Day Ceremony</title><description>The City of Carrollton will hold a wreath-laying ceremony on Monday, May 27 at 10 a.m. to honor fallen U.S. military personnel who have given their lives in service to the nation.
All are welcome to join Carrollton Mayor Steve Babick and City...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4735/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:16:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4735/?date=20240523021600</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Receives 2024 Municipal Traffic Safety Award</title><description>The City of Carrollton Municipal Court received a 2024 Municipal Traffic Safety Awards Honorable Mention in April from the Texas Municipal Courts Education Center (TMCEC).
The award is given to a municipal court in recognition for outstanding...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4733/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:31:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4733/?date=20240522033100</guid></item><item><title>Free Summer Breakfast and Lunch Program Begins May 28</title><description>School’s out for the summer, and that means hundreds of local children will be looking for places they can meet their friends, have fun, and eat healthy meals. 
The free Summer Food Program is ready to meet the demand. Carrollton’s Parks and...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4732/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:25:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4732/?date=20240520052500</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Swears In City Councilmembers, Certifies Charter Revs</title><description>The results of the General Election and Special Charter Election on May 4 were canvassed and certified during the Tuesday, May 14 meeting at City Hall. 
All four of the Carrollton City Council seats from the May 2024 General Election ballot were...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4725/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:21:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4725/?date=20240515032100</guid></item><item><title>Cleanup Carrollton? Challenge Accepted</title><description>Be a part of the pollution solution by volunteering to remove trash and debris from the environment to help Carrollton’s streets, waterways, and green spaces thrive.&amp;nbsp;
The City is taking part in the Spring 2024 North Texas Community Cleanup...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4707/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:28:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4707/?date=20240510072800</guid></item><item><title>City of Carrollton Retains Multiple ‘AAA’ Ratings on Bonds</title><description>Fitch Ratings, Inc. and S&amp;amp;P Global Ratings independently assigned a “AAA” rating to the City of Carrollton’s general obligation (GO) improvement and refunding bonds, waterworks and sewer system revenue bonds, and the outstanding bonds in each...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4721/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 08:23:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4721/?date=20240509082300</guid></item><item><title>Unofficial Results of Carrollton General &amp; Special Election Are In</title><description>The unofficial election results for the May 4 General and Special Charter Election are in. 
Results remain unofficial until City Council canvasses the votes at the Tue., May 14 Council Meeting. 
For more information on the 2024 election results,...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4719/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:37:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4719/?date=20240506013700</guid></item><item><title>Vote in the General Election Saturday May 4</title><description>The City of Carrollton will hold a General Election and Special Charter Election on Sat., May 4 to elect Council places 1, 3, 5, and 7 and to consider proposed changes to the City Charter. To vote in the May 4 election, you must have registered to...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4664/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:45:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4664/?date=20240502064500</guid></item><item><title>Book Reading Goals with the 2024 Summer Reading Challenge</title><description>The Carrollton Public Library presents the 2024 Summer Reading Challenge (SRC) running from Saturday, June 1 through Thursday, August 1 and includes age-specific reading programs for&amp;nbsp;everyone.&amp;nbsp;Register now at...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4716/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:35:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4716/?date=20240501023500</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Chosen for National Sustainability Leadership Program</title><description>The City of Carrollton has been selected by the U.S. Green Building Council (USGBC), the leading authority on green building and global developer of the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design (LEED) green building program, as one of 12 cities...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4717/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:35:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4717/?date=20240501023500</guid></item><item><title>Register Day of for Carrollton Tails &amp; Trails 5K Race or 1-Mile Walk</title><description>Preregistration is over, but participants can still register on race day. Park at Creekview High School (3201 Old Denton Road) to register and be bused to the starting line on the Blue Trail. Race day registration and warmup will be held from 7-7:45...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4665/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:25:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4665/?date=20240423092500</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton Residents Will Soon See Woodlake Lake Improvements</title><description>Woodlake Lake (near the corner of N. Josey Lane and E. Peters Colony Road) will undergo site renovations thanks to Carrollton residents who voted in the 2018 Bond Election for Parks &amp;amp; Recreation Improvements.
The approved $22.4 million-Parks...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4710/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:18:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4710/?date=20240422111800</guid></item><item><title>Carrollton City Council Approves Community Funding Policy</title><description>City Council approved a resolution on Tuesday, April 16 updating the Community Funding Policy, combining the existing Community Services Policy and Community Events Policy into a single document and application.&amp;nbsp; 
The purpose of the policy is to...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4709/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:45:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4709/?date=20240419104500</guid></item><item><title>Don't Miss Carrollton Women's First Responder Day April 20</title><description>Discover the Bond of Courage and Service

Calling all service-minded young women: Explore what it means to be part of a close-knit family of first responders dedicated to safeguarding the City of Carrollton.
This recruitment-based event,...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4669/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:33:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4669/?date=20240419103300</guid></item><item><title>DART Construction at the Downtown Carrollton Station on N. Broadway</title><description>Dallas Area Rapid Transit (DART) is in Phase II of the reconstruction of the rail crossings and adjacent roadway along N. Broadway Street and N. Denton Drive with a southbound, left-lane closure of N. Broadway Street 24/7 from Tuesday, April 16...</description><link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4336/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:30:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4336/?date=20240418013000</guid></item></channel></rss>