<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Carrollton News RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/</link>
<description> This is the syndication feed for City of Carrollton, TX. Carrollton News</description>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:18:02 -0500</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Reports Positive Mosquito Traps</title>
<description>Click to view PDF&nbsp; Dallas County Health and Human Services (DCHHS) has confirmed five mosquito samples testing positive for West Nile Virus (WNV) in Carrollton. The samples were collected from...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4746/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4746/?date=20240805035000</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton’s Newest Leisure Connections Magazine is Available</title>
<description>Carrollton’s Leisure Connections recreation magazine is now available at&nbsp;Rosemeade Recreation Center,&nbsp;Crosby Recreation Center,&nbsp;Josey Ranch Lake Library,&nbsp;Hebron &amp; Josey Library, the Carrollton Senior Center,&nbsp;City Hall,...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4767/</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4767/?date=20240801081400</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Severe Weather Cleanup Updates</title>
<description>August 1 5:30 p.m. The City’s storm debris collection service, which included outside contracted assistance, is now complete. Crews have collected debris from neighborhoods as well as City parks, roads, and other public spaces for an estimated total...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4737/</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4737/?date=20240801053300</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>DART Construction Closures on W. Belt Line Road at Hutton Drive</title>
<description>Dallas Area Rapid Transit (DART) contractors will close the inside lanes of W. Belt Line Road at Hutton Drive on Monday, August 5 until Thursday, August 22 (weather permitting) as part of a three-phase DART Silver Line construction project, and will...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4336/</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4336/?date=20240801030200</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bring An Appetite to the Carrollton Culture Fest on the Square</title>
<description>Grab the family and come out for an adventure around the world in Historic Downtown Carrollton (1106 S. Broadway Street) on Saturday, September 28 from 3-9 p.m. for the Carrollton Culture Fest. The previously known World of Foodies event has been...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4765/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4765/?date=20240731042400</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Learn. Serve. Improve. Applications Open for Boards & Commissions</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton is now accepting applications for 2024 Boards &amp; Commissions appointments. Residents are encouraged to get involved in the areas of community life that mean the most to them. Members make a difference: City governments...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4764/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4764/?date=20240731042400</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Selects New Assistant City Manager Shannon Hicks</title>
<description>After a nationwide search, the City of Carrollton has chosen Shannon Hicks to serve as Assistant City Manager. Hicks will assume his role in Carrollton effective Monday, August 26, replacing former Assistant City Manager Marc Guy, who retired in June...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4763/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4763/?date=20240731041400</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton’s Pooch Pool Party to Bring a Tail-Waggin’ Good Time</title>
<description>Say goodbye to the dog days of summer at the City of Carrollton’s annual Pooch Pool Party on Saturday, September 7 from 10 a.m. to 3 p.m. at the Rosemeade Rainforest Aquatic Complex (1334 E. Rosemeade Parkway). Bring your dog out for swimming and...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4759/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4759/?date=20240724041100</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>NTTA Closing The Addison Tunnel Nightly Through August 29</title>
<description>NTTA TRAFFIC ADVISORY Nightly Closures for NTTA Maintenance: These closures are needed to complete tunnel upgrades. July 21-August 29 from 8 p.m. to 6 a.m. (Nightly): East- and westbound Addision Airport Toll Tunnel (AATT) will be closed to...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/3766/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 08:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/3766/?date=20240722082300</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Offers Expanded Access to Business Contracts through Ion Wave Application</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton has partnered with Ion Wave, a state-of-the-art procurement solution, to provide a simple-to-use interface for suppliers interested in bidding on goods, services, and engineering projects. The application allows companies to...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4757/</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4757/?date=20240718033700</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Wins National Communications Awards</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton’s Marketing Services team was honored to win four first-place 2024 Blue Pencil and Gold Screen Awards for marketing and communications efforts from the National Association of Government Communicators (NAGC).&nbsp; The Blue...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4755/</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 12:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4755/?date=20240716123500</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>DART to Reduce Weekend Rail Service in Dallas During Repairs</title>
<description>Passengers traveling in Dallas’ Central Business District via DART may experience delays over at the weekends of June 28-July 1 and July 12-15 as necessary maintenance is performed on DART Rail’s high-voltage power source — or catenary — via a...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4753/</link>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4753/?date=20240630021600</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Marketing Services Wins Three State Awards</title>
<description>&nbsp; The City of Carrollton Marketing Services Department was honored to be recognized with three state marketing and communications awards, including two first-place awards,...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4751/</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 08:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4751/?date=20240627082300</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>City Council Increases Senior and Disabled Homestead Tax Exemptions</title>
<description>Carrollton City Council voted unanimously to approve an amendment to an ordinance increasing the senior and disabled tax exemptions from $87,000 to $97,000 at the Tuesday, June 25 meeting. The ordinance as amended is effective immediately and applies...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4750/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4750/?date=20240626042800</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Selects New Pro Tem Positions</title>
<description>&nbsp; &nbsp;Mayor Pro Tem Richard Fleming &nbsp; &nbsp;Deputy Mayor Pro Tem Christopher Axberg...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4749/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4749/?date=20240626042400</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Volunteer for Carrollton’s CARE Team</title>
<description>Carrollton stands as the first city in Texas to adopt the groundbreaking 4 Minute City™ Program. This initiative aims to equip CPR-trained citizen volunteers with AEDs, thereby reducing the time required to provide lifesaving care to patients...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4659/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 08:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4659/?date=20240626082700</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Ranks Among the Top Safest Cities Nationwide</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton ranks among the top 25 safest cities nationwide on GOBankingRates’ “50 Safest and Most Affordable US Cities To Live In” report. According to GOBankingRates’ May review of the largest U.S. cities by population, Carrollton has...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4743/</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4743/?date=20240618042400</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Seeks Citizen Input for Downtown Expansion</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton is expanding its Downtown Master Plan to develop the area near the Dallas Area Rapid Transit (DART) Green Line Light Rail. Don’t miss the opportunity to make a difference. The objective of the expansion is to build on the...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4706/</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 09:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4706/?date=20240611093700</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton to Provide Special Collection of Storm Debris</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton has contracted with current provider Republic Services and CrowderGulf Disaster Recovery &amp; Debris Management to conduct a special collection of storm debris at residential addresses, beginning Monday, June 3....</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4741/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4741/?date=20240603013000</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton to Host Eighth Annual Paws on the Square Event</title>
<description>Bring the whole family, both furry and otherwise, to Historic Downtown Carrollton (1106 S. Broadway Street) on Saturday, June 8, from 9 a.m. to noon, for a tail-wagging good time at the City’s eighth annual Paws on the Square. This free,...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4713/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4713/?date=20240603010000</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Festival at the Switchyard Vendor Applications Now Open</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton has opened applications for craft and food vendors to participate in the 14th annual Festival at the Switchyard on Saturday, November 2 from 11 a.m. to 10 p.m. in Historic Downtown Carrollton (1106 S. Broadway Street). The...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4729/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4729/?date=20240603124800</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Trinity River Authority Sanitary Sewer Outflow Notice Due to Heavy Rain</title>
<description>The Trinity River Authority has notified the City of Carrollton that its Central Regional Wastewater System treatment plant experienced a wastewater outflow in its collection system on Tuesday, May 28, that exceeded 100,000 gallons. It occurred in an...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4739/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4739/?date=20240529040300</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Take Carrollton's Parks & Recreation Master Plan Survey</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton is updating its Parks, Recreation, and Open Space Master Plan, and is gathering input from residents on what they envision in the years ahead for their children and for themselves.&nbsp;&nbsp; TAKE THE SURVEY Survey is...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4677/</link>
<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4677/?date=20240528091300</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton to Hold Memorial Day Ceremony</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton will hold a wreath-laying ceremony on Monday, May 27 at 10 a.m. to honor fallen U.S. military personnel who have given their lives in service to the nation. All are welcome to join Carrollton Mayor Steve Babick and City...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4735/</link>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4735/?date=20240523021600</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Receives 2024 Municipal Traffic Safety Award</title>
<description>The City of Carrollton Municipal Court received a 2024 Municipal Traffic Safety Awards Honorable Mention in April from the Texas Municipal Courts Education Center (TMCEC). The award is given to a municipal court in recognition for outstanding...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4733/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4733/?date=20240522033100</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Free Summer Breakfast and Lunch Program Begins May 28</title>
<description>School’s out for the summer, and that means hundreds of local children will be looking for places they can meet their friends, have fun, and eat healthy meals. The free Summer Food Program is ready to meet the demand. Carrollton’s Parks and...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4732/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4732/?date=20240520052500</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Carrollton Swears In City Councilmembers, Certifies Charter Revs</title>
<description>The results of the General Election and Special Charter Election on May 4 were canvassed and certified during the Tuesday, May 14 meeting at City Hall. All four of the Carrollton City Council seats from the May 2024 General Election ballot were...</description>
<link>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4725/</link>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid>https://www.cityofcarrollton.com/Home/Components/News/News/4725/?date=20240515032100</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
